I get a little nihilistic towards the end.
Emptiness?
Is your body getting used to that kind of show business?
I'd like to get used to it.
You're so cute.
It's frustrating, but cute?
She's cute.
You're so cute when you come here sometimes.
So cute!
I gave up after one bite.
Of course you did.
Yes, I did.
I gave up after one bite.
Oh, yeah?
I want to see how pretty you are.
Sweaty face?
Next time
Night Time Room
Well, here we are. I'm Yagami, who grew up in a cider solo hot water room until I visited Mima.
Today's guest is a very special girl.
The most popular girl of the season is here. This is the wind. Please come in.
The morning chime has rung.
This is Nakamura Yuna, attendance number 17 from Ebeichi Junior High School.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you. Nakamura-san.
I am attendance number 17.
Do you have a preference for what you want people to call you?
You have a talent.
Do you have such a request?
I don't know.
I've always been called "Mr. Nakamura".
Do you prefer to be called Nakamura or something like that?
Do you prefer Nakamura-san?
I prefer "Nakamura-san".
I will continue to challenge you as Ms. Nakamura. Please call me Ms. Nakamura.
Even to customers.
Nice. It's new.
There is no one like you.
He is from Fukuoka Prefecture.
He is the first person from a local area in Ebichu since Kokumu-san from Aichi City.
I heard this through a rumor.
You are still living in Fukuoka, aren't you?
I still live in Fukuoka.
When I have work or lessons, I come to Tokyo and come back to Fukuoka.
Isn't that a lot of work?
I commute from Fukuoka and take lessons.
And you performed on stage the other day.
How was it? How was it?
I was really nervous before I got on stage.
But once I got out on stage and started dancing, I wasn't nervous at all.
The rest was nothing but fun.
How are your sisters? How are your seniors?
Are they
They love you?
Very much.
Who's on track to be the top?
Mayama-san.
Mayama-sensei, you're the oldest.
When I first met you, you were in junior high school.
You were in elementary school, right?
That's great. How are you doing? What do you think of Mayama-sensei?
He is very kind, and he teaches me very carefully what I don't understand in lessons.
That's great.
I talked with my senpai a little bit.
We talked and got to know each other quite well.
We all got to chat with each other.
Do you chat with them?
What do you talk about when you are that far apart?
But we talk a lot about work.
Sometimes we talk about work, and sometimes we talk about performance.
Sometimes we talk about performance.
If you have any advice on how we should do today's shoot, please let me know.
Who gave you that advice? I don't know.
But I get a lot of advice from Mr. Maiyama.
I see. What did Mr. Mayama say? I don't know how to do this job.
But I try my best to smile and be myself.
That's the right answer.
That's what Maizan-san is all about.
Be yourself. Are you doing it now? Smiling.
But I've been speaking with a smile lately.
Recently?
I've been talking so much that I've started to make a straight face. My facial muscles are gradually dying.
I see.
Recently, I've been smiling properly.
Normal. Not all the time, that's okay.
I love this picture so much that I can't live without it.
This program was provided by Cordier, Barton Size Custom, Hirofumi, Tsukasa, and Ragnegi.
Hirofumi-san, Tsukasa-san, and Ragunegi-san.
Thank you very much.